https://www.insight-corp.com/privacy-policy/

Sign In
Search for:
Disclaimer; Information Reuse; Policies
© 2020 Techgradient and/or its Affiliates.
All rights reserved.
Insight Research Corporation is a trademark of Techgradient.
Disclaimer
The contents of this web site represent our analysis of the information generally available to the public or released by responsible individuals at the companies mentioned. It does not contain information provided in confidence by our clients. Since much of the information in our research is based on a variety of sources that we deem to be reliable, including subjective estimates and analyst opinion, Techgradient does not guarantee the accuracy of the contents and assumes no liability for inaccurate source materials.Techgradient disclaims liability for incidental or consequential damages and assumes no responsibility or liability for any loss or damage suffered by the buyer as a result of the use or misuse of any of the information or content of this website. Techgradient assumes or undertakes no liability for any loss or damage suffered as a result of the use, misuse or reliance on the information and content of this website.
Information Reuse
The information contained on this site is provided solely for the purpose of your evaluation of Insight's reports and services and may not be reproduced in any form. However,Techgradient does consider your making a limited number of copies of this web site for the sole purpose of furthering your evaluation as being a fair use of the copyrighted material contained herein, including electronically transmitting such copies to your colleagues as necessary to complete your evaluation, but no portion of the material copyrighted herein may be reprinted or published in any form without the prior written consent of Techgradient. Please contact info@insight-corp.com or call us for more information.
Privacy Policy
Welcome to our Privacy Policy
Your privacy is critically important to us.
The terms “Techgradient”, “Insight Research Corp” and “Insight Research” are used interchangeably.
Techgradient is located at:2201, World Trade Center, Brigade Gateway Campus Malleswaram Bengaluru 560055 India.
It is Techgradient’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://www.insight-corp.com (hereinafter, "us", "we", or "https://www.insight-corp.com"). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Techgradient collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Techgradient ’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Techgradient ’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Techgradient may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Techgradient also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://www.insight-corp.com blog posts. Techgradient only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Techgradient ’s websites choose to interact with Techgradient in ways that require Techgradient to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Techgradient gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we may ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://www.insight-corp.com to provide a username and email address.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Advertisements
Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Techgradient and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Links To External Sites
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party sites, products or services.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Techgradient discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Techgradient ’s behalf or to provide services available at Techgradient ’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Techgradient ’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Techgradient will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Techgradient discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Techgradient believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Techgradient , third parties or the public at large.
If you are a registered user of https://www.insight-corp.com and have supplied your email address, Techgradient may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new reports, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Techgradient and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Techgradient takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Aggregated Statistics
Techgradient may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Techgradient may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Techgradient does not disclose your personally-identifying information.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Techgradient may use "Cookies" and other similar technologies to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Techgradient uses cookies to help Techgradient identify and track visitors, their usage of https://www.insight-corp.com, and their website access preferences. Techgradient visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Techgradient ’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Techgradient ’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Techgradient 's use of cookies.
E-commerce
Those who engage in transactions with Techgradient – by purchasing Techgradient 's services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Techgradient collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfil the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Techgradient. Techgradient does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described above.
Privacy Policy Changes
Techgradient may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Techgradient ’s sole discretion. Techgradient encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Cancellation and Refund Policy
The contents of individual market research reports represent our analysis of the information generally available to the public or released by responsible individuals at the companies mentioned. It does not contain information provided in confidence by our clients. Since much of the information in our research is based on a variety of sources that we deem to be reliable, including subjective estimates and analyst opinion, Techgradient does not guarantee the accuracy of the contents and assumes no liability for inaccurate source materials. Techgradient disclaims liability for incidental or consequential damages and assumes no responsibility or liability for any loss or damage suffered by the buyer as a result of the use or misuse of any of the information or content of this study. Techgradient assumes or undertakes no liability for any loss or damage suffered as a result of the use, misuse or reliance on the information and content of this study.
Consequently, no claims for refund will be entertained once the report manuscript is delivered to the customer either in electronic format and/or in hard copy. Reports are delivered to the customers upon confirmation of payment in forty-eight working hours of the confirmation of payment. Payment once made, cannot be cancelled.
We started in 1990, and have seen, chronicled and analyzed the crests and troughs of the telecommunications industry. Along the way, we published close to two hundred market research reports, along with numerous custom consulting assignments.
Quick Links
Home
About Us
Careers
Reports
Blog
Privacy Policy
Newsletter
2201 World Trade CenterBrigade Gateway CampusMalleswaramBengaluru 560055 India
+1 973 541 9600, +91 80 6793 5731
marketing@insight-corp.com
Social Media
Copyright © 2020 Techgradient., and / or its Affiliates. All Rights Reserved. | See our Privacy Policy.
